[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&GT；&GT；Kyle：让我们谈谈我们可能如何选择解决这个问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Let's talk through how we might choose to solve this problem.
当这个回调被调用时，我们将得到一个响应，并且
When this callback is called we're going to get a response back and
由于关闭，我们将知道它来自三个文件中的哪一个。
because of closure we gonna know which one of the three files it came from.
大家都看到了吗？
Does everybody see that?
所以我可以做的是我可以有一个句柄响应函数
So what I could do is I could have a handle response function that I
调用它得到的文件名和文本，好吗？
call out to with the file name and the text that it got, okay?
现在我可以直接在这里做代码，但我要把它推到
Now I could do that code directly inside of here but I'm pushing it out to
另一个函数，这样我的嵌套就少了一点。
another function so that I have a little bit less nesting going on.
现在，处理响应接收
All right now, handle response receives
的文件名和一些内容
a file name and some contents for
文件，每个人都在跟踪吗？
the file, everyone following that?
我需要的是封闭范围内的东西，
And what I'm going to need is something in closing scope,
在这种情况下，可能是全局范围，一些变量，
in this case probably the global scope, some variable,
一些要跟踪返回的响应的对象，
some object that is going to keep track of the responses that have come back,
以防我在我能够呈现它之前得到回复。
in case I get a response back earlier than I'm able to render it.
每个人都同意我的观点吗？
Everybody with me on that?
我可能会得到一个回复，并且能够立即呈现它，但我要
I might get a response back and be able to immediately render it but I'm going to
我需要一些东西来保持我得到的回复，但我还不能呈现。
need something to hold on to the responses that I get back that I can't yet render.
我需要能够，基本上，遍历这个集合
And I'm going to need to be able to, basically, iterate over that collection of
该打印出来的时候做出回应，打印出我得到的任何东西。
responses when it is time to print things out and print out whatever I've gotten.
所以我要做的就是有一个叫做响应的变量，
So the way I'm going to do that is simply have a variable called responses,
我们会把它变成一个物体。
and we'll make it an object.
无论如何，这都不是解决这些练习的唯一方法。
This is not, by any means, the only way to solve these exercises.
就像我们在这些工作坊中做的几乎所有事情一样，
As with almost everything we do in these workshops,
有很多不同的方法来切割它。
there's many different ways to slice it.
我只是在给你做心理建模的一种方法，好吗？
I'm only walking you through one way of modeling this mentally, okay?
因此处理响应可以
So handle response could
如果响应文件名。
say if responses of filename.
这是一个属性为文件名的对象，
That is an object whose property is the filename,
使用的URL(如果尚未设置)。
the URL that was used if that's not already set.
所以也许我会这样做，而不是将响应作为文件名，
So maybe I would do that instead of response as a filename,
也许我会说，如果不是文件名的回应。
maybe I'll say if not filename in responses.
所以我确定了一个事实，这个函数是用响应调用的
So I make sure for a fact that this function is getting called with a response
我还没见过。
that I haven't yet seen.
这可能会处理函数在某种程度上被双重调用或
This takes care of maybe the function somehow getting double called or
随便吧？
whatever, right?
所以我要说这是一个我还没有看到的回应。
So I'm gonna say this is a response that I have not yet seen yet.
因此，第一步肯定是将其添加到我的对象中。
So the first step is definitely to add it to my object.
我正在把它存储到一个对象中，
I'm storing it into an object,
好吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle：文件名是属性
okay? &gt;&gt; Kyle: File name being the property
对象上的位置，内容是我放入对象中的值。
location on the object, contents being the value that I'm putting into the object.
因此，如果这是file1，如果这是第一次调用，并且
So if that was file1, if this was the first time this is being called, and
这是file1，我可以在响应中迭代这些内容。
that was file1, I could iterate over the stuff in responses.
如果有东西要渲染，我可以立即渲染。
And if there was stuff to render, I could immediately render it.
把它从响应的对象中取回来。
Take it right back out of the response's object.
或者，在这种情况下，我可能只是将文件二放入，而文件一还不在那里
Or I might have just put file two in and file one isn't yet there in which case
我还不能继续，我只需要把它留在那里，然后再试一次，好吗？
I can't go on yet I just need to leave it there and try it again later, okay?
请记住，此句柄责任被调用了三次。
Keep in mind this handle responsibility called all three times.
所以我们每次收到AJAX响应时都会调用
So we called every single time we get an AJAX response back is going to get called
所以这三个都有机会被调用。
so it's going to have an opportunity to be called for all three.
但是我们不确定哪种顺序有六种不同的方式可以发生或者
But we're not sure which order there's six different ways that this can happen or
三种不同的方式什么的。
three different ways or whatever.
有很多不同的方式可以发生这种情况
There's a lot of different ways this can happen and
我们不确定哪个订单会发生，所以
we're not sure which order is going to happen and so
我们正在尝试协调或正常化该并发性。
we are trying to coordinate that or normalizing that concurrency.
所以在我确定我的回应是
So after I've made sure that my response has been
存储到我的回复中的内容已经存储在回复中。
stored into my responses in the contents have been stored in the responses.
现在我可以简单地从一个数组开始。
Now I could simply start out with an array.
现在，这是一种简单的作弊方式。
Now, this is a simple cheat way of doing it.
当然，还有其他方法我可以把它们保存在
There are, of course other ways where I could've kept those in
在某种程度上是外部位置，但是
a external location in some way but
我只是想找出解决这个问题的最简单的方法。
I'm just trying to come up with the simplest way of solving this problem.
如果我知道这些URL是什么，并且我知道它们应该按照什么顺序发生。
If I know what those URLs are, and I know what order they're supposed to happen in.
我可以按照请求的顺序生成这个数组，
I could have produced this array by the order that they were requested in,
如果那是我想要的，再一次，只是采取简单的方式。
if that's what I wanted, again, just taking the simple way.
假设我知道file1、file2、file3需要按此顺序发生。
Let's assume that I know that file1, file2, file3 need to happen in this order.
所以现在我可以说，for(var i=0)。
So now I can just say, for( var i=0).
我小于arr.length，也许不是arr，也许我会将其称为
I less than arr.length and maybe instead of arr maybe I'll call this
文件名。&gt；&gt；Kyle：I+SO
filenames. &gt;&gt; Kyle: I++ so
我将查看文件1。
I'm going to look at file1.
它将是i的文件名，第一次迭代将是文件一。
It's going to be filenames of i which the first iteration is going to be file one.
我要说如果这是平分的话
I'm gonna say if that is even
Responses对象。
the responses object.
所以文件名i在响应中或者不在响应中。
So filenames of i is in responses or it's not in responses.
如果没有回复，有人能猜出我要做什么吗？
Can anybody guess what I'm going to do if it's not in responses?
打破for循环。
Break the for loop.
实际上在这种情况下
Actually in this case for
为了方便起见，我要回去了，完全空了。
convenience sake I'm just gonna return just completely empty out.
所以无论我在哪种情况下，我是否正在查看file1，并且它不在那里。
So whichever case I'm in whether I'm looking at file1 and it's not in there.
或者我正在查看文件2但它不在其中，或者我正在查看文件3和
Or I'm looking at file2 and it's not in there, or I'm looking at file 3 and
不在里面。
it's not in there.
在这个特殊的过程中，我没有任何东西可以通过我的回答来呈现。
I've got nothing left to render on this particular pass through my responses.
因为我知道如果它不在那里我就不会呈现其他任何东西。
Cuz I know if it's not there I'm not gonna render anything else.
所以我可以利用提前回来的机会。
So I can take advantage of an early return here.
如果它在里面的话。
If it is in there.
我可以说，如果它还是。&gt；&gt；Kyle：例如，
I can say, if it's still. &gt;&gt; Kyle: For example,
我可以说它是否仍然是一个真值，或者我可以说它是否仍然是一个字符串。
I can say if it's still a truthy value, or I could say if it's still a string.
一会儿你就会明白我为什么这么说了。
And you'll see why I'm saying that in a moment.
如果它仍然是一个字符串，那么我知道是时候继续渲染了。
If it's still a string then I know it's time to go ahead and render this.
所以我会说文件名，我会说i的文件名的响应。
So I'll say filenames I'll say responses of filenames of i.
这一个将需要与i的文件名的响应相同的事情。
This one is going to need to be the same things as responses of filenames of i.
现在，现在我已经渲染了。
Now, now that I've rendered it.
我想将条目留在那里，但我想将其标记为已渲染。
I want to leave the entry in there but I want to mark it as having been rendered.
因此，将其标记为已渲染的简单方法是将其从
So a simple way of marking it as having been rendered is to change it from being
文字。
the text.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：到类似于false的东西。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: To something like false.
所以条目仍然在对象中，
So the entry is still in the object,
这意味着我不会试着把它读进去。
which means I'm not going to try to readd it in there.
但我不会尝试重新渲染它
But I'm not going to try to re-render it over and
一遍又一遍，因为它将不能通过这个打印错误检查。
over again, because it's going to fail this typo check.
有上百万种不同的方式可以选择来实现这个逻辑。
There's a million different ways that you could choose to implement this logic.
我只是向你展示一种可能的表达方式。
I'm just showing you one possible way of saying.
我正在重复这个列表，我正在检查是否需要渲染
I'm living over this list and I'm checking to see whether I need to render
一些东西。&gt；&gt；Kyle：最后，
something. &gt;&gt; Kyle: At the end of this,
如果我已经渲染了所有三个，&gt；&gt；Kyle：那么我可以
if I have rendered all three of them, &gt;&gt; Kyle: Then I can
最后输出我的完整信息。&gt；&gt；Kyle：这
finally output my complete message. &gt;&gt; Kyle: This
这三次函数都会被调用。
function is gonna get called for each of those three times.
令人高兴的是，它被file1调用一次，并且
The happy path is that it gets called once with file1 and
然后使用file2一次，然后使用file3和
then once with file2 and then once with file3 and
它永远不需要提前归还，而且每个人都需要存储东西。
it never needs to get to this early return thing and every needs to even store thing.
但它可能先用file3调用一次，然后先用file2调用一次，然后
But it might get called once with file3 first, and then once with file2 first, and
最后是第三次使用file1，它还没有呈现任何东西。
then finally the third time with file1, where it hasn't rendered anything yet.
第三次，当它循环通过时，它会说我确实有
And that third time, when it goes to loop through, it's going to say I do have
一个file1渲染，我有一个file2渲染，我有一个file3。
a file1 render, I do have a file2 render, I do have a file3.
所以无论从哪种方式来看，我都会尽快渲染，但是
So which every way these come in, I'm always going to render asap but
仅以正确的发音顺序。
only in the correct articulated order.
是啊。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：SO
Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
我也许理解那些出了问题的护理人员，但是
I maybe I understood the params that went wrong but
我记得你说过你想通过改变回调或者
I thought you said you wanted to do it by altering the callbacks or
你不是这么说的吗？&gt；&gt；kyle：你什么意思？
did you not say that? &gt;&gt; Kyle: What do you mean?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：所以我在想也许我们
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So I was thinking maybe we
我们是否会对所有GET文件有不同的回调和
would we have different callbacks for all of the get files and
然后不知何故我们会审计它们。&gt；&gt；Kyle：我们有
then somehow we would audit them. &gt;&gt; Kyle: We do have
所有Get Giles的不同回调。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，
different callbacks for all the get giles. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay,
那很好&gt；&gt；Kyle：我不确定我明白什么
that's fine &gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm not sure I understand what
你是说。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：i
you mean. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I
没想到会有这种恐吓。&gt；&gt；Kyle：你用不同的方法解决了吗？
wasn't expecting this intimidation. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Did you solve it a different way?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不，我不能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No I couldn't.
凯尔：好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Okay.
&gt；&gt；发言人2：我在想
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I was thinking
更多的是关于回调的开始和一些他们的承诺
more along the lines of Promises about the start of the callback and something they
什么都想不出来。&gt；&gt；Kyle：好吧，你唯一能做到的
couldn't come up with anything. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Well the only way you're going to
最终排序的回调是有顺序请求的。
end up ordering the callbacks is to have sequential requesting.
其中，在file1完成之前，您甚至不会请求file2。
Where you don't even request file2 until after file1 is finished.
这违反了问题设置的基本前提之一
Which violates one of the fundamental premises of the setup of the problem which
就是按顺序给他们打电话。
is to call them in order.
这就是为什么它在那里，因为它很容易，如果你只是想做连续请求。
That's why that's there because it's easy if you just wanna do serial requesting.
但正是并行请求导致了这种并发协调
But it's the parallel requesting that causes this concurrency coordination
变得更复杂好吗？
to be more complex, okay?
这里真正提出的观点是，三个独立的回调必须
The point that's really being made here is that three independent callbacks have to
共享一些闭包状态，即使它是一个全局变量。
share some closure state even if it's a global variable.
他们将不得不共享一些关闭状态来协调自己。
They're gonna have to share some closure state to coordinate themselves.
只是，没有别的办法了。
That's just, there's no other way around it.
无论是全局状态还是有其他的包装器变量
Whether it's the global state or whether there's some other wrapper that variables
不管你怎么切都会传给我。
passed to me no matter how you slice it.
必须有一些共享的可变成本三个回调。
There gonna have to be some shared variable cost all three callbacks.
他们必须潜在地在这个变量中存储一些东西
And they're gonna have to potentially store something in that variable
直到了回来拿到它的时候。
until it's time to come back and get it.
这就是我们说我们正在协调并发的意思，
That's what we mean by saying that we're coordinating concurrency,
我们正在管理时间状态复杂性。
is that we're managing that time state complexity.
我们可以看到有一个解决方案，但我不认为任何人会争辩
And we can see that there's a solution to it but I don't think anybody would argue
这是一个很好的优雅的解决方案，对吗？
that this is a good graceful solution to it, right?
很难看，对吧？
It's ugly, right?
但它能完成任务。
But it gets the job done.
我无法告诉你几百次我解决了类似的问题
And I can't tell you many hundreds of times I've solved similar problems in
过去，我唯一可用的工具就是函数和
the past where the only tool I had available to me was functions and
闭包变量。
closure variables.
所以我们可以完成这项工作，甚至复杂的某些领域。
So we can get the job done, even complex certain areas.
但这不是理想的模式，这就是为什么我要带你通过它。
But this isn't the ideal pattern and that's why I'm walking you through it.
我给你看，首先，
I'm showing you, first,
我们一直在处理的痛点激发了我们想要更好的原因
the pain points that we've been dealing with to motivate why we want better
Patterns.q每个人都同意我的观点吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle：有吗？
patterns.q Is everybody with me on that? &gt;&gt; Kyle: Any
关于练习一的其他问题？
other questions about exercise one?
我们会一遍又一遍地回到完全相同的问题域
We're gonna get to come back to the exact same problem domain over and over and
再来一次，好吗？
over again, okay?
用更好的方法解决这个问题，你会变得越来越好
You'll get better and better at solving this problem with better
模式。&gt；&gt；演讲者3：顺便说一下，
patterns. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: By the way,
我不确定你会不会返回，比如如果它返回file2，
I'm not convinced that you're going to return at, like if it comes back file2,
file1，file3我想你可能会在file2之后完成，
file1, file3 I think you might get to complete even after file2,
因为它不会掉下去吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle：对不起，
cuz won't it fall through? &gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm sorry,
什么？&gt；&gt；扬声器3：你不会得到完整的
what? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Won't you get the complete
如果它返回，我们假设是file2，file1，然后是file3。
if it comes back, let's say file2, file1, and then file3.
但是在您获得File2之后，它应该打印出来并通过输出下降
But after you get file2, it should print out and fall down through the output
完成，然后您就完成了，然后file3应该返回，然后再获取另一个
complete and then so you get complete then file3 should come back then get another
完成。&GT；&GT；Kyle：你还在失去我，
complete. &gt;&gt; Kyle: You're still loosing me,
也许在休息的时候我们可以谈谈-&GT；&GT；演讲者3：是的。
maybe over a break we can talk- &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我的意思是你可以比较我
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I mean you can compare what I've
在这里键入我在解决方案文件中键入的内容。
typed here to what I typed in the solution file.
解决方案文件客观上是正确的，并且
The solution file is objectively correct, and
也许我错过了什么，但我很确定这三次传球中的一次会
maybe I missed something, but I'm pretty sure one of those three passes is gonna
在它击中输出完成之前击中那个东西。
hit that thing before it hits the output complete.
您要么可以遍历整个for循环，要么
You're either gonna be able to go through the entire for loop or
你会打到这个案子，这会阻止它完成。
you're gonna hit this case, which stops it from getting to complete.